Guide to the International Brigades Archive, Moscow: Selected Images ALBA.PHOTO.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Folder 179: Photo Album of 15th International Brigade in Preparation for Brunete Offensive; Photographed by Yugoslavian Volunteer, Major Vladimir Stefanovich
  - [Soldier seated, reading, next to rocks; other troops visible in background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179144)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/144
  - [Men crouched by hillside, one in foreground reading], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179145)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/145
  - [Troops on hillside path through foliage], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179146)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/146
  - [Long shot line of troops marching along dirt road], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179147)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/147
  - [Ravine with dense foliage], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179148)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/148
  - [A ruined tank, run partially off the road, tread destroyed], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179149)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/149
  - [Long shot tank in open field], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179150)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/150
  - [Tank in grassy field, soldiers stand nearby, two tanks visible in far background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179151)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/151
  - [Tank with damaged tread sitting at roadside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179152)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/152
  - [Damaged buildings, rubble], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179153)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/153
  - [Edge of settlement, damaged buildings with rubble on ground], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179154)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/154
  - [Damaged buildings, rubble], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179155)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/155
  - [Damaged buildings, rubble], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179156)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/156
  - [Abandoned village street/square], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179157)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/157
  - [Destroyed buildings, rubbled], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179158)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/158
  - [Large gathering of men at field next to damaged buildings], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179159)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/159
  - [Damage buildings along dirt street], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179160)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/160
  - [Low stone wall in field, mountains in distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179161)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/161
  - [Rugged hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179162)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/162
  - [Hilltop view with boulder overlooking open plain, distant town, hills], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179163)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/163
  - [Open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179164)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/164
  - [Soldier sleeping under a blanket in a trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179165)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/165
  - [Treetops, sky, trench wall], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179166)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/166
  - [Trench wall with man under blanket], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179167)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/167
  - [Treetops, sky, trench wall], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179168)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/168
  - [Two stone bridges over a ravine], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179169)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/169
  - [Boulders with shelter(?) built next to them], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179170)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/170
  - [Skinny trees, rugged countryside, mountains in distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179171)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/171
  - [Low stone wall, powerlines visible at top of frame], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179172)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/172
  - [Bend in road through open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179173)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/173
  - [Small hill, rugged countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179174)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/174
  - [Open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179175)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/175
  - [Open countryside, stone walls], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179176)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/176
  - [Officers in chairs, troops seated on ground listening], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179177)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/177
  - [Soldiers gather around the back of a transport vehicle], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179178)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/178
  - [Small shelter (?) next to a cluster of trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179179)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/179
  - [Line of troops gathering smoething from ground/bushes], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179180)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/180
  - [Super-wide shot of open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179181)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/181
  - [Wide shot tree-lined dirt road, mountains in background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179182)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/182
  - [Super-wide shot of open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179183)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/183
  - [Super-wide shot of open countryside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179184)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/184
  - [Dead body laid out next to blankets], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179185)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/185
  - [Dead body in trench], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179186)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/186
  - [Three dead bodies laid out on grass], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179187)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/187
  - [Body in death position, left shoe knocked off and lying next to head], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179188)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/188
  - [Rugged hillside, soldiers in midshot], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179193)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/193
  - [Troops looking in the bushes, trying to pull a horse struggling on the gravel], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179194)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/194
  - [Horses underneath a small tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179195)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/195
  - [Dead horse on rocky hillside], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179196)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/196
  - [Rifles propped up against tree, men seated in shade in background], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179197)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/197
  - [Top of a big tree], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179198)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/198
  - [Trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179199)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/199
  - [Men watch as horse feeds], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179200)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/200
  - [Low stone wall alongside a dirt road], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179201)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/201
  - [Chain-link fence overlooks rugged hillside with a winding path], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179202)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/202
  - [Open countryside, distant hills], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179203)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/203
  - [Dirt road through scrubby foliage, distant hills], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179204)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/204
  - [Dead body, stomach exposed], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179209)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/209
  - [Dead body, hard to see face], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179210)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/210
  - [Dead body partially covered in brush], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179211)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/211
  - [Open countryside, tanks (?) visible in distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179212)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/212
  - [Open plain, troops visible in distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179213)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/213
  - [Open plain, large group of troops visible in distance], undated (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 177_179214)
    Moscow Number: 5/179/214
- Folder 180: 15th International Brigade during Operations for the Republican Army, 1937-1938
  - [Shot out doorway (?) of tank in field], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180002)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/2
  - [Two soldiers ready in a trench], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180003)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/3
  - [Large mass of soldiers marching out of a town on a dirt road], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180004)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/4
  - [Mass of soldiers moving up hillside], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180005)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/5
  - [Group of soldiers poses near wall/rock outcropping], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180006)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/6
  - [Truck, car approach soldiers along dirt road on the side of a hill], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180007)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/7
  - [Four soldiers with two machine guns on the side of a road], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180008)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/8
  - [Heavy cannon in field with troops], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180009)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/9
  - [Group of soldiers poses on ledge], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180010)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/10
  - [Officer addresses small group of soldiers, artillery crew at work], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180011)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/11
  - [Two men speaking closely face-to-face (hard to see)], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180013)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/13
  - [Officers, soldiers pose with small cannon], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180014)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/14
  - [Soldiers in combat gear relax behind stone wall], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180015)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/15
  - [Men sit on ledges in front of stone building, large tree, horse visible to the left], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180016)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/16
  - [Group of soldiers hauling heavy armored gun], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180017)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/17
  - [Seated soldier reads newspaper, other sit chatting behind him], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180018)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/18
  - [Men stand against wall behind destroyed artillery], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180019)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/19
  - [Troops behind sandbag wall on a ridge with artillery], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180020)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/20
  - [Large mass of soldiers being addressed by an officer], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180021)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/21
  - [Men riding horses across barren countryside], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180022)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/22
  - At Fuentes [four men at a snow-covered riverbank, three on the ground to drink from the river], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180023)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/23
  - [Smoke rises from lakeside camp. Two trucks, large tent visible], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180025)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/25
  - [Line of men marching across snowy countryside], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180026)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/26
  - [Line of men snakes across snow-covered land], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180027)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/27
  - [Line of men making their way over a hill in the snow], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180028)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/28
  - [Soldiers march into town as people gather to watch], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180029)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/29
  - [Men with gear gathered around the back of a truck], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180030)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/30
  - [Soldiers working near foot of a mountain], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180031)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/31
  - [Open field with heavy cannons, troops, bunker entrance visible in top-left], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180032)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/32
  - [Men digging out hillside camp], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180037)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/37
  - [Three officers in fround of destroyed buildings], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180038)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/38
  - [Two soldiers in a trench], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180039)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/39
  - [Wide shot three soldiers moving across terrain], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180040)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/40
  - [Officers,soldiers, other people gathered outside a large door], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180041)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/41
  - [Bundled-up troops on the march], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180042)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/42
  - [Five men in winter gear, one with rifle, one rolling cigarette], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180043)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/43
  - Transmission Crew (Before Breakup at Meeting), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180044)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/44
  - [Troops in winter gear shoveling], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180045)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/45
  - [Soldiers digging a trench with pickaxes], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180046)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/46
  - [Soldier reads a note while standing by sandbag wall], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180047)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/47
  - 15th International Brigade Auto Park, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180048)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/48
  - [Two men read/write while a third looks on], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180049)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/49
  - [Men sitting in trench, man in foreground reading], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180050)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/50
  - [Men stand guard by a fence], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180051)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/51
  - [Large group of soldiers on the march], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180052)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/52
  - [Long line of men stretching along a wall], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180053)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/53
  - [Men with rifles in a trench, one lining up a shot], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180055)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/55
  - 15th International Brigade Auto Park Machine Shop, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180056)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/56
  - [View through trees of two tanks], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180060)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/60
  - Recruits in Training Camp, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180061)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/61
  - [Colorguard in front of large formation of men], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180062)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/62
  - [Small cannons in front of group of soldiers in formation], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180063)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/63
  - [Large transport flatbed with equipment and men on it], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180064)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/64
  - Breakfast at 15th International Brigade "Operations" Department, Ebro Front, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180065)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/65
  - [Lone tank in middle of a field, one man standing on it and another beside], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180067)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/67
  - [Group of soldiers posing with a tank], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180068)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/68
  - [Super wide shot open plain with tanks, men visible in distance], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180083)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/83
  - [Troop in poncho, another in jacket next to him, another wrapped in blanket behind them], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180084)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/84
  - [Soldier sitting with rifles in improvised shelter], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180085)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/85
  - [Soldiers on guard from mountain lookout], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180086)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/86
  - [Small group of troops walking away from camera, one in crouch], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180087)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/87
  - [Soldiers lined up against a wall, eating], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180088)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/88
  - [Men standing near a small stone wall], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180089)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/89
  - [Group of soldiers on lookout, one with binoculars], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180090)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/90
  - [Officers address troops seated in circle around them], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180091)
    Moscow Number: 5/180/91
  - Commander Copic (Presenting Awards for Distinguished Service at Quinto and Belchite; Taken Near Huesca), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 177_180092)
    General
    Moscow Number: 5/180/92
- Folder 181: 15th International Brigade during Operations for the Republican Army at the Ebro, Feb 1938-Jun 1938
  - [Card: "Republic Espanola, XV Brigada Internacional, Comisariado De Guerra" (scan cut off?)], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181001)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/1
  - Crossing the Ebro, Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181006)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/6
  - [Troops with a raft and barrels on a riverbank, attempting to rig a ferry line across the river], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181011)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/11
  - [Troops line the riverbank, pulling on a line], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181012)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/12
  - [Troops work by riverbank], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181013)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/13
  - [Soldiers getting into a rowboat, some men wading into river to launch boat], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181014)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/14
  - [Full rowboat being deployed into river], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181016)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/16
  - [Launching a rowboat onto the Ebro], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181017)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/17
  - [Ebro, Construction of a ferry or a pontoon bridge(?)], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181018)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/18
  - [Rowboats being launched on the Ebro. Boat in center of image with donkey on board], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181019)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/19
  - [Launching a rowboat onto the Ebro. Duplicate of ALBA Photo 11-1703], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181020)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/20
  - 15th International Brigade Engineers (Working on Fortifications at Ebro Front) [digging a trench], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181023)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/23
  - Brigade Parade at Tarazona [troops at attention], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181024)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/24
  - After Fascist Air-Raid (Seguro de la Banas) [two soldiers drag a body from rubble near a stone wall], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181027)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/27
  - Staff Kitchen [three men preparing a meal in large pots, table in open air], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181029)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/29
  - Transmission Class (Ebro Front) [small groups of men sitting on ground around a tree], Feb 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 177_181030)
    Moscow Number: 5/181/30
- Folder 182: 15th International Brigade in Training
  - 5/182/1: Cabo School [shooting from prone position while crowd watches large group of soldiers in a field], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182001)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/1
  - 5/182/2: Cabo School [three riflemen and machine gun crew], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182002)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/2
  - [Soldiers exercise with rifles, one soldier leading the ranks], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182003)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/3
  - [Camoflaged soldier poised to throw weapon at swastika-emblazoned tank for training exercise], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182004)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/4
  - [Officer demonstrates exercise on rope bridge between trees to group of soldiers], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182005)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/5
  - [Soldiers perform training exercise on rope bridge between trees], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182006)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/6
  - 5/182/7: Cable across Ebro [men pulling the cable for bridge (?)], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182007)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/7
  - [Soldier next to four women in dresses], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182008)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/8
  - [Shirtless soldiers jogging with rifles], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182009)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/9
  - [Rifle gripped in soldier's hand], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182010)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/10
  - [Soldier assembling rifle with tool], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182011)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/11
  - [Soldier assembling rifle with tool], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182012)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/12
  - [Rifle with butt resting on ground, trigger area wrapped in cloth], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182013)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/13
  - [Men building a pit trap for tank], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182014)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/14
  - [Troops peer over sandbag wall at tank, driven halfway into pit trap. Training exercise], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182015)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/15
  - [Two soldiers prepare to attack tank, training exercise. One soldier with bottle, one with grenade], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182016)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/16
  - [A swastika-emblazoned tank used in training. Appears in other photos], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182017)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/17
  - [A soldier works on his weapons], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182018)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/18
  - [Soldier cleaning his rifle], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182019)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/19
  - [Men conducting rope-bridge exercise], undated (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 177_182020)
    Moscow Number: 5/182/20
- Folder 183: Portraits of 14th and 24th Battalion Volunteers, 1937
  - Preparing for Exercises; Zizkovaci at the Front, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183005)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/5
  - Dimitrov Battalion, Group of German Volunteers, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183007)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/7
  - "Hit the Fascists with Machine Guns," Zizkovaci Company at the Aragon Front, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183008)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/8
  - [Soldier with helmet and glasses rests against dirt wall], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183009)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/9
  - "We Shall Always Win," Zizkovaci Company in Formation at the Aragon Front, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183010)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/10
  - Comrades of Dimitrov Battalion, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183011)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/11
  - Dimitrov Battalion [five soldiers], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183012)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/12
  - [Woman and children with Spanish aviators (?)], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183013)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/13
  - [Group of soldiers in a trench], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183014)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/14
  - [Soldiers gathered in trench, one smoking cigarette], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183015)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/15
  - [Three soldiers conversing], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183016)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/16
  - Milos Sedlar at Irun, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183017)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/17
  - Tabaroff [two soldiers, one with arm in sling, and a woman in a dress], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183018)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/18
  - Dimitrov Battalion, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183019)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/19
  - Dimitrov Battalion [with dog], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183020)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/20
  - Italian Company of the Dimitrov Battalion; Lieutenant Now with Dombrowski Battalion; Klein, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183021)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/21
  - [Soldier with helmet and glasses poses in front of an unreadable sign], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183022)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/22